worldchess.com 2017-01-28

# Privacy Policy | World Chess | News, ratings, events in a chess world

**What personal information do  we collect from the people that visit our website?**  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do  we collect information?**  
We collect information from you when you register on or enter information on our site.

**How do  we use your information?**  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:  
      — To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.  
      — To improve our website in order to better serve you.  
      — To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.  
      — To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.  
      — To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

**How do  we protect visitor information?**  
Your Account information will be protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to help prevent unauthorized access to your Account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your Account.

We seek to protect Account information to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any Account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

**Do  we use ’cookies’?**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**We  use cookies to:**  
      — Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.  
      — Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some features may be disabled.

**Third-party disclosure**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third-party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

We have implemented the following:  
      — Google Display Network Impression Reporting  
      — Demographics and Interests Reporting

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**How does our site handle do  not track signals?**  
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**  
It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**  
We do not specifically market to children under 13.

**Fair Information Practices**  
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
      — We will notify the users via e-mail notification within 7 business days  
      — We will notify the users via in-site notification within 7 business days

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us via [privacy@worldchess.com](mailto:privacy@worldchess.com)
